{
    "subject": "resource/I'm_No_Dummy",
    "predicate": "ontology/distributor",
    "object": "resource/NBCUniversal",
    "human_readable": "I'm No Dummy is distributed by NBCUniversal.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9322070479393005,
            "question": "What is the connection between NBCUniversal and 'I'm No Dummy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9286199808120728,
            "question": "Are there any other shows besides 'I'm No Dummy' distributed by NBCUniversal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8155784010887146,
            "question": "Name a show distributed by NBCUniversal."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8042896389961243,
            "question": "Who distributes the show 'I'm No Dummy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7658987641334534,
            "question": "Is NBCUniversal involved in distributing television shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6800792217254639,
            "question": "Can you give an example of another show distributed by NBCUniversal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6638772487640381,
            "question": "What company is responsible for distributing 'I'm No Dummy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6472769975662231,
            "question": "Does NBCUniversal distribute only television shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4903776943683624,
            "question": "What type of media company is NBCUniversal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14821624755859375,
            "question": "What does it mean for a company to 'distribute' a television show?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=I'm No Dummy is distributed by NBCUniversal.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5749_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of media company is NBCUniversal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5749_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does NBCUniversal distribute only television shows?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5749_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What company is responsible for distributing 'I'm No Dummy'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5749_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5749_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5749_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5749_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5749_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5749_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5749_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5749_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5749_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5749_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5749_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because one of the articles mentions \"I\u2019m No Dummy\u201d by NBCUniversal, which suggests that the documentary \"I'm No Dummy\" is distributed by NBCUniversal."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The text mentions \"I\u2019m No Dummy\u201d by NBCUniversal, which supports the distribution of the comedy/documentary by NBCUniversal."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}